ABOUT ME

Having completed Diploma in Maximedia from NIIT, I commenced my career, Sep 2004, with Bookmyshow as a web designer. During my tenure here, had the opportunity to develop many html layouts and also learned to work on PHP, MYSQL.

Feb 2008, I joined webinfinity as a sr. web developer, leading a team of 4 developers and 3 Designers. In recognition to my ethical work practice, I was recognized with a promotion to Manager in April of 2008. During this space of my tenure, I have had the opportunity to work with the senior management on aspects of project management, planning, budgeting, web, app systems and resource management.

To take a leap in reaching my career goal in June 2017, I joined Lusail Media as a Technical Lead. Here my role was to manage and develop from scratch to fully working products for my organization and clients, thus achieving business goals.

Jan 2021; I Joined Acclivis Technologies Pvt Ltd. As a consultant, I have strong communication and influence strategies in the areas of Web & APP developments and also its Project Management and implementation, business development, finance and branding. Experienced in managing, supervising with excellent organizational and communication skills. I am Selfmotivated, enthusiastic, analytic, versatile professional with team building, and strong problemsolving skill, and project development and management experience. Strong work ethic, demonstrating pride in performance and successful work accomplishment.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Currently working with Acclivis Technologies Pvt Ltd. As a Consultant since Jan 11th 2021 till Date.

Worked with Lusail Media - Doha. As a Technical Lead since June 17th 2017 till Dec 15th 2020.

Worked with webinfinity. As a Project Manager since Feb 7th 2008 till May 2017.

Worked at Bigtree Entertainment Pvt. Ltd (Network 18 group) as a senior Web Designer & Developer since 20th September 2004 till Feb 2nd 2008.

Worked with Antenna e- mobile solutions as a Sr.Web Designer and Graphic designer. From 24th May 2004 – 15th September 2004.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:

Course	School/Institution	Year
Maxi Media	NIIT - Diploma	2006
H.S.C	K.V. No-1, Naval Base, Kochi	2003 -2004
S.S.C	K.V. No-1, Vasco Da Gama, Goa	2001-2002

Technology expert:

PHP, HTML, React Native, Ionic, React JS, MySQL, WordPress, Joomla, Blockchain Technology, Python, Android & IOS App development (Flutter), jQuery, SEO & SMM

Digital Marketing:

Google AdWords, Inbound HubSpot Marketing, Bing Accredited Professional

Total Exp:

12+ Years

Current Designation:

Web and Mobile App developer

Server:

Google Cloud, AWS cloud server, Alibaba Cloud server & digital ocean Cloud server.

Below are some of my LIVE projects

New Web projects in Doha

- a) https://www.fish.qa
- b) http://www.moodgatar.com/
- c) https://aaiga.com/
- d) https://www.greenwood.qa/
- e) https://www.tamapp.co/
- f) https://www.pinggr.com
- g) https://www.dragonmall.co
- h) https://www.bollmanattestation.com

Mobile Application List:

1) Rafeeg (Technology - Ionic-v3)

Brand Brief: Rafeeq is an online platform developed & customized in-house in the state of Qatar to cater the local logistic needs using technology.

Client Requirement:

- They want to be bridge between vendors and consumers.
- Items offered by the vendors can be viewed, customized, ordered and tracked.
- Drivers will collect the items and deliver them directly to the consumers.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.
- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.
- Continuously suggest improvements for the development team.
 Advise and mentor other developer.

2) Fish.qa (Technology - Ionic-v3)

Brand Brief: Fish QA is an online platform to compare prices from different sellers, and make your order for the best quality and price.

Client Requirement:

- They want to be bridge between vendors and consumers.
- Items offered by the vendors can be viewed, customized, ordered and tracked. Drivers will collect the items and deliver them directly to the consumers.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.
- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.
- Continuously suggest improvements for the development team.
 Advise and mentor other developer.

3) the ENTERTAINER (Technology - Ionic-v3)

Brand Brief: The ENTERTAINER is the moneysaving app that's packed with the 2-for-1 offers everyone wants.

Client Requirement:

- friends and family to save every day.
- Friends can share offers thanks to the PING feature.
- Track all the money you've saved with our savings calculator.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.
- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.
- Continuously suggest improvements for the development team.
 Advise and mentor other developer.

4) Akly - Healthy Food Delivery (Technology - Ionic-v4)

Brand Brief: deliver foods from Healthalicious restaurants with on-demand meals or subscribe to ready made plans to achieve your goals

Client Requirement:

- On-demand or subscription offer.
- Items offered by the vendors can be viewed, customized, ordered and tracked. Drivers will collect the items and deliver them directly to the consumers.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.
- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.
- Continuously suggest improvements for the development team. Advise and mentor other developer.

5) Snoonu — Delivery (Technology - Ionic-v3)

Brand Brief: Snoonu is the fastest shopping & delivery app in Qatar consisting of restaurants, grocery stores, retail shops.

Client Requirement:

- Order food & groceries from multiple shops.
- View menus with items pictures.
- Items offered by the vendors can be viewed, customized, ordered and tracked.
- Drivers will collect the items and deliver them directly to the consumers.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.

- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.
- Continuously suggest improvements for the development team.
- Advise and mentor other developer.

6) Wishbox Online (Technology - Flutter)

Brand Brief: Wishbox is one of the best online food delivery applications in Qatar that aims to provide food and grocery items efficiently.

Client Requirement:

- Complete food and grocery delivery services.
- Free delivery services.
- Offers rewards
- Items offered by the vendors can be viewed, customized, ordered and tracked.
- Drivers will collect the items and deliver them directly to the consumers.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.
- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.
- Continuously suggest improvements for the development team.
- Advise and mentor other developer.

7) Bookmyshow (Technology – PHP, MYSQL)

Brand Brief: Bookmyshow is one of the best online movies & events ticketing applications that aims to provide movie, events tickets.

Client Requirement:

- Complete movie tickets & events services.
- Free online ticket services.
- Offers rewards
- Items offered by the company can be viewed, customized, ordered and tracked.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.
- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.

Continuously suggest improvements for the development team.

- Advise and mentor other developer.

Currently Working Mobile App

1) Tam App (Technology - Flutter)

Brand Brief: Tam APP is an on-demand doorstep service, repair and maintenance platform. A one-stop solution for all your needs.

Client Requirement:

- Doorstep service team.
- Multi-brand vendors.
- Offers rewards
- Items offered by the vendors can be viewed, customized, ordered and tracked.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.
- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.
- Continuously suggest improvements for the development team. Advise and mentor other developer.

2) PlazaHollandi (Technology - Flutter)

Brand Brief: Plaza Hollandi is one of the key business units of Al Maktab Al Qatari Al Hollandi W.L.L.

Client Requirement:

- Doorstep delivery team.
- Multi-franchise area wise.
- Offers rewards
- Items offered by the franchise can be viewed, customized, ordered and tracked.

My Contribution:

- Understand and execute release management and change management for changes to business application.
- Provide leadership on project development, projects designing.
- Create and test prototypes and keep up with new technology in the industry that brings innovation.
- Work with build team to manage build configurations.
- Continuously suggest improvements for the development team.
- Advise and mentor other developer.